I'm seeing people claiming they're Black Panthers or Black Panther affiliated, but that Black
Panthers don't stand for illegals. I'm seeing people calling themselves Black Panthers who
are not co-signed by the Black Panthers. How about this? Why can't y'all start your own organizations?
Why? Because the name Black Panther is trusted. And so you want people to automatically trust you
when in actuality, you should be starting from scratch and encouraging and engaging in order
to earn that trust the same way the Panthers did. They had consistent presence in communities
across the world. I'm paraphrasing, but number eight of the Black Panther 10-point program is
we are against the oppression of all people. So we want the end to the oppressing.
That's not just for Black people. That said, we need more organizations based on the framework
of the Panthers that provide constituency services as well as militarized protection. However, knowing
the effort of the oppressor to infiltrate, there has to be an organic growth that is made in generosity
and in connection and coalition with other organizations. We need all different kinds of
organizations that are for the decolonization of the people. And we don't need them to be called the
Black Panthers. We need to use the spirit and the realities and the work of the Black Panthers to inspire us
in this new era to build organizations that grow upon the work of the Panthers, but address the uniqueness of our realities.
The surveillance on another level, the capitalism on another level, the negligence of the Black community by the Black
bourgeoisie. There is so much that you don't need to use the Black Panther's name. You just need to let
their ancestral wisdom and their failures lead us to create new organizations that create new ways to dismantle
these systems and free us from the new prisons that they have put us in. Support a real one.